closetsamples.com 2016-06-26

# Privacy Policy - Closet of Free Samples

Closet of Free Samples (further referenced as “CFS,” Closet Samples “our,”  “us,” or “we”) is for entertainment purposes only. However, we strive to protect our readers (further reference as “you,” “users,” or “readers”) privacy in every way possible.

**Freebies**

All offers listed on Closet of Free Samples are available to our readers to the best of our knowledge at the time of publication. Closet of Free Samples is not responsible for any damages caused either directly or indirectly as a result of using links provided on the site. Closet of Free Samples is also not responsible for any misprints, incorrect information, typographical errors, or omissions in any of the content, material and free offers listed. We are, however, responsible for being funny and/or witty and claims full responsibility for making you laugh.

Closet of Free Samples does not send out any free merchandise, nor do we guarantee, approve or endorse any offers listed. We simply find free stuff, contests and coupons then list them for your convenience. Closet of Free Samples is not responsible for the shipment of goods and/or services. We make no guarantees as to the quality or value of the products or services offered from our advertisers. If you have any problems or questions about a freebie, please contact the original vendor that shipped the freebie.

Please make sure you have read any fine print and / or restrictions carefully before you sign up for, purchase, accept, or enter any offer. It is your responsibly to be cautious when giving personal information online.

If a freebie or link is posted on Closet of Free Samples and misrepresents the offer, please [contact us](http://www.closetsamples.com/advertising-pr/contact-us/) and we will remove the content in question.

**Information Collected About You**

While visiting our site, the following information is collected and stored:

  * Your IP address
  * All pages located on Closet of Free Samples that you visited
  * The length of time spent browsing our site

Furthermore, if you choose to leave a comment, the following information is also stored:

  * Your name
  * Your email address

We do _not_ record nor store any personal information, such as but not limited to your home address, full name, birth date, or telephone number.

Any information that we collect is _never_ shared with, sold, rented, leased, or traded to any outside 3rd party. The information is only used for administrative and technical purposes by employees of Closet of Free Samples.

**3rd Party Advertising and Cookies**

Advertising on Closet of Free Samples is handled through a variety of affiliates and ad sites. In order to serve these ads, some may use DoubleClick DART cookies. When users visit Closet of Free Samples and either view or click an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher’s site(s) and across the web.[Google’s own privacy policy](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=100557&sourceid=aso&subid=ww-ww-et-asui&medium=link) states the following:

> * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
>  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
>  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

If you have any questions or concerns, please take the time to further read up on Google’s privacy policies.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time in the future. We will not reduce your rights under this privacy policy without notification and your explicit consent.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Here is a url for more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.
